<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<books>
    <book ID="ArenaBook1" Title="{{W|The complete History of The Glorious Arena of The Exiled}}" Format="Auto" Margins="1,2,2,2" Load="Merge">
    <page> Although the history of the great Sultans is an ongoing campaign for our scribes, the magnitude of the events and the stories shared within these walls deserve a great place in the annals of Cud. In this brief book, I will try to relate the history of this sacred Crysteel Temple. 

    </page>
    <page>II.

Created by the great Sultan Killer of Bees, the arena first served as a palace that housed the Sultan's family. The section that later became the notorious arena was originally a greenhouse used by Killer of Bees to harvest Eater's flesh. The reasons for these actions by the Sultan remain unclear, but the mushrooms led to the inevitable collapse of the family and the Sultan's power.
    </page>

    <page>III.

It is said that on the 13th day of Uulu Ut in the year 1309, a strange fungus-like creature came to the Crysteel Palace, reclaiming a debt from the Sultan. As no one was there, the wards claimed that the creature began to incrust the palace itself. The last thing the wards ever said before they were sentenced to death was that a cloud of strange orange spores surrounded and blinded them. On this day, the palace was destroyed inside, as if the creature had stolen everything in the greenhouse, tearing everything in its way.
    </page>

    <page>IV.
    
    Although nobody claims that the fall of the palace was a problem for the Sultan, it became an opportunity for pilgrims and travelers, who could now seek shelter in the palace. Over the years, the place changed a lot, and from time to time, people from every corner came to witness the palace. For some strange reason, the pit that served as the greenhouse became our beloved arena—the place where heads and hearts are broken and torn every day, where battles among brothers decide the tides of stakes, and where wine and cider never stop pouring.
    </page>
    </book>
</books>